okay we're going to do some lamb room
until about 8:30 okay until about 8:30
and then we're gonna do some real app
presentations thank you
so I'm gonna continue with the book
we're at Nick were 2 6 8 a 2 6 8 a
Eamonn why I D s mo and okay they're not
just on copper chamber so he quotes some
copper he's starting the 15th day of the
teaching and he's quoting some copper
Teta combat : Sola human communication
in Senko the Tibetan you know tuning and
disengaging Kabbalah how do we know we
have the right attitude about life when
we can recognize sansara then sansara
means our circle right
what's the circle in the two husbands in
the kitchen we allowed our kids we make
a bad seed next week we come home
husband says bad thing to us then we
answer the husband we plant a new bed
scene next week the kids are bad
this means samsara ok this is suffering
you can break it with the pen ok Oh
husband come from me then I won't say
bad word back to him
I want to break this cycle okay
so then when we walk around the world
when we go to Bangkok tomorrow you know
you're gonna see the airport everybody
there is traveling somewhere why are
they traveling somewhere
they want something okay so you will see
in the airport maybe hundreds of people
from many different countries then you
have to when you're in the airport don't
waste your time especially if there's a
long line at the airline you can do
sansara meditation standing in the line
you know sometimes you have half-hour 45
minutes you can do sansara meditation
everybody in this room everybody in this
airport they came to the airport because
they want something then it's a human
nature okay when you want something
let's say I want mala human nature
training for 50,000 years if I want a
rosary what I'm I talked to my arm what
you go over there why I want the money
okay let's get the mother then it's a
most basic human nature I will I will
take it and I will bring it close to my
body and I got a mother this is human
nature fifty thousand years okay now
when I when I do this
am I making new seeds or am I using all
this well using old seed mainly when I
take now that's answer in the airport
okay everybody want to go somewhere to
get something to bring it to myself in
this system
don't be seed burner be seed maker I
[Music]
love this rosary okay
understand okay it's the most basic
human thing okay it seems stupid oh I
pay money to come to Thailand guess I'll
go like this it seems foolish to teach
[Music]
but it's the most deep thing okay when
human being wants something we and we
bring to me now after you came to this
routine if you like the rosary okay get
to some money I make a new seed okay
make a new see okay it's very difficult
it's so simple it's difficult okay : k
then somewhat captain's issue could this
or chip and I did time Jamie top onion
then he says the teacher also when the
teacher gets up on the seat Oh
[Music]
everybody's nice to get not everybody
gets flower to kiss now
everybody gives a red envelope to guys
now thank you thank you for reading long
way but the teacher said we have to
think it's it will finish okay I will
also finish this retreat will finish
everything's moving so the teacher has
to take the medicine during the class
okay I also will change I also will
leave you know so when you teach
remember who you are you you are lucky
to teach but you won't live forever you
will also pass the time Jamie topping
determined una reunión the engine name
in the Machine nominee your chest
submission so it's good when you teach
to remember my friend I think it was
although although from Mexico
I don't know if you remember I remember
where are you you gave a teaching I was
there he said when you see your friends
and you go to the movie together then
when the movie finished and you go home
Aldo said I remember say goodbye to them
as this it's the last time you will see
them in your life because maybe it will
be okay
[Music]
then I thought it was very sweet there's
a couple years ago I still remember
when you say goodbye to someone do with
love because maybe you won't see them
again in this life
okay this is the first song I played in
one year in the guitar you know I
couldn't play for one year
why last Christmas we played in our
place with our good friends and the
drummer three days later he went to the
restaurant next to our college and Thai
Thai restaurant and he's eating dinner
with my other student there are a couple
he died like like that he's young you
know he's normal person I was in Beijing
I got phone call two o'clock in the
morning
there's no killer what my husband dying
next to me right now what he's dying
right now in the restaurant is he dead
no but I think I'm going to he just
breathe a little bit ambulance is coming
you know what should i do what should i
do yeah you know say some prayer then
five minutes later he died he died while
I'm on the telephone then we couldn't
play for one year we feel every time we
play with we remember him okay so when
you meet your friends when you go home
tomorrow
say goodbye with a lot of in-law
we don't know if we can meet again okay
so sweet not depressed okay but a happy
sweet okay this way we have to be sweet
with each other we don't know if we see
each other okay
then I'm going to be someone I'm not
chicken I get up chip a couch at a run
draped in the new it's or Sangeetha
coupon in there I wanna chance and my
line in general imagine mm Shimon tittle
good sangguk opening they wanna so this
idea when you're at the airport you know
you see your friend for the last time
maybe they will die okay then this is a
kind of love for one other person but in
the airport tomorrow several thousand
people will say goodbye to several
thousand people then think about it you
know don't just love the person from
this retreat that you say goodbye
but I make a prayer for everybody in
their port many husbands are saying
goodbye to their wife I will see you
next week but we don't know if they will
see them next week many people are
saying goodbye to their parents parents
are going on a vacation
many parents died on vacation so think
about the whole airport you can use the
time it feels like waste of time to
stand in the line to wait right but a
Buddhist person we love traffic jams we
we love long lines at the airport we can
do meditation it's actually you are very
lucky you can think Buddha made a
traffic jam for me Buddha made a long
line for me so I can have love for all
the people in the airport who are saying
goodbye to people they know
and maybe they won't meeting it if you
want to make that if if the line is very
slow it means if you are very lucky you
can make the meditation deeper okay this
lama said here you can make the
meditation deeper each of the husband
saying goodbye to their wife in this
airport today
each family saying goodbye to their
mother and father today at their port
[Music]
every child in the hand of every mother
in this airport in the past life they
have been my mom you know we are having
so many beautiful performances you know
we had a lot of we just had a Mexico
performance the Russian performance was
awesome Russia Kazakhstan Ukraine it was
amazing and then the Singapore Malaysia
then the Germans were pretty good
especially the meditator German okay it
looks like we are different people you
know where's this one from what country
is this one from you can guess or this
one from I think Malaysia this one from
Indonesia this one from Russia okay but
all of them have been your mother not
one time million times there's a joke in
jing each person in this room cleaned
your poo poo many times
when you were baby and each man and
woman in this room gave you milk from
the chest it feels a little strange you
play rock n roll with Stanley and then
thank you for feeding me melted but it's
true okay so when you're at the airport
maybe somebody will push you maybe
somebody will go in front of you feel
happy oh my mom came to the airport my
mom in front of me go ahead mom maybe
you will be in the airport until to the
next day can I be around and they're
coming changing them you became a
comedian common method me soppec
everything and Jim Gilliam Couture chic
today Gilda keeping us sing together Chu
Chu a topic you're joshing if you think
like that then standing in the line to
check in your luggage
you are making seed to become a Buddha
okay so don't think you can only
practice at your house and your
meditation cushion sometimes you can
have a better meditation in the airport
okay
while you're waiting then you don't
waste your time if you are irritated you
know how many people here you know why
can't the airline hires more worker you
know you can feel irritated at the
airport okay it's okay it's correct or
you can plant a seed for Buddhahood
standing in the luggage light so you
decide okay I think this one is very
powerful probably you can remember
tomorrow okay in the line it's kind of
strange feeling every ugly guys your mom
gave you milk okay then then in the line
at the airport you are making seed from
your Buddhahood
[Music]
okay lang kita kita boots chairman Cheng
you know Mikey keep on the parquet work
on checking eternity McGarry my thought
picture Kovac Corner corner corner in
day so most people when they do good
thing to other person it's a cause for
samsara okay they're not making there's
a we call dirty good seed and a pure
good seed and a good good as pure good
so there's two kinds of seeds batson and
a good sin inside the good sin there's a
there's a good good seed and there's a
bad good seen the bad good sin keep you
in sensor so what's the difference
$300 $300
wait what'd you say almost that's $100
anything 300 what makes a good good seed
and what makes a bad good steam $300
chin some Chin's are you ready first
gentle that's a better answer than the
answer I was thinking so I agree $300
for you
[Applause]
her good good seat is better than my
good good thing okay thank you
okay I'm gonna repeat what she said even
if you understand the pen okay there's
two ways you can use to make good seats
okay okay so I have I have rosary okay
then I like them they're very good for
hitting your husband
I mean to do the prayer and I like to
have a rosary then I can think her her
bad good see if I give this rosary to
shopping I will get pin I will get 10
roses okay so she said this is a bad
good scene you're just thinking about
your stuff
you understand the pimp you understand
to plant the seed but your goal is it
just for yourself yeah take the row
three I want ten okay I want ten and I
hope other people will follow my example
what bad good see good good thing I want
to be virus I want to be like the guy in
Oslo who didn't kiss all the girls in
the restaurant okay I want to be example
for other people then this system will
spread because of my example both are
good comer
okay shopping I want to give this team
okay have I hope you enjoy you will get
10 rosaries but they have a number limit
limit 10 only 10 okay in this system not
enough in this system 10 times not
enough okay now here's a good good I
will give her rosary because I want more
and I pray people will watch me oh he's
giving rosary did he got many real 3
he's helping other person make money he
got a lot of money I will also try I
will also help the old lady in the
nursing home because he got a nice
partner and other people watch you Wow
he's very successful maybe I will try
okay we call infinite Karma infinite
karma Y fan copy fan fan copy fan fan
copy fan fan copy friend no limit no
limit okay that karma never finished it
keeps growing okay forever it will go
around the world many people will copy
other people people will use the seed
because you are successful two ways to
teach you should use the four steps
first way second way haha look at my
girlfriend she's cool you also want go
to the nursing home
okay then that's a better teaching show
other people your happiness show other
people your success practice yourself
people will then you become teacher
automatic teacher of course people will
copy you because you are successful you
have lots of money
you have beautiful family you're healthy
when you are 65 years old okay then of
course people will follow you
okay and that's a good good karma and
your answers better than my answer I
thank you I bought we're gonna do a
finish Mandela Jasmine and then we're
going to have our real out so we have
enough from Taiwan Sarah best inverter
my seller no I think she's in the line
at the airport
oh here she comes she's getting exercise
awesome
[Music]
okay well anyway funk song one-minute
catch breath okay let's go shiver here -
she thought she knew
some you shader me
don't sing
cherry pies
you know that Mandela and the
the Walker said I mention tautology
tarnishing there too many
well I mean
[Applause]